Guide to the Susan A. Henry papers, 1998-2010.
Henry, Susan A. papers, 1998-2010
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Susan A. Henry papers, 1998-2010.
21-1-3456
Susan A. Henry
11 cubic ft.
Reports, Financial Records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains departmental annual reports, budget reports, committee reports and core program summaries.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Dr. Henry is the Ronald P. Lynch Dean Emerita of Agriculture and Life Sciences.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains departmental annual reports, budget reports, committee reports and core program summaries.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Henry, Susan A.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences--Administration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to office of origin.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Reports
Series II. Meetings and Conferences
Series III. Outreach, Programs, and Initiatives
Series IV. Retreats
Series V. Videos
Series VI. Speeches
Series VII. Gifts
Series VIII. Subject Files
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Reports
  - Advisory Council Members, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Center for the Environment, Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - CIIFAD, Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Department Annual Reports - Book 1 (1), 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Department Annual Reports - Book 1 (2), 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Department Annual Reports - Book 2 (1), 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Department Annual Reports - Book 2 (2), 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Department Annual Reports (1), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Department Annual Reports (2), 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report - Sr. Associate Dean's Office, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Budget Cuts (1), 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Budget Cuts (2), 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Workforce Planning Initiative for Finance - Pre-Implementation Plan, June 2003 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Named Professorships - Nominations (1), 2003 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Named Professorships - Nominations (2), 2003 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Named Professorships - Nominations (3), 2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dept. of Landscape Architecture - Self-Evaluation Report (1), March 2004 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Dept. of Landscape Architecture - Self-Evaluation Report (2), March 2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dept. of Landscape Architecture - Self-Evaluation Report (3), March 2004 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Dept. of Landscape Architecture - Self-Evaluation Report (4), March 2004 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dept. of Food Science - Self-Evaluation Report, October 2004 (Box 8)
  - Land Grant Mission in CALS Task Force Briefing Materials, October 2006 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Plant Sciences Task Report, May 2007 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Plantations - Forest Home - Deer Management Report (1), 2006 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Plantations - Forest Home - Deer Management Report (2), 2006 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Orientation for New Chairs, September 2007 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2008-2009 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2005-2006 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2004 -2005 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report to the Provost, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - CALS Environmental Task Force, 2000-2009 (Box 19, Folder 11, 12, 13)
  - Undergraduate Biology Curriculum Task Force- Meeting Minutes, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Biology Curriculum Task Force Report, 2006-2008 (Box 19, Folder 15-17)
  - Task Force Report on Improving CALS Farms, Field Stations and Plant Growth Facilities, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Biological Curriculum Transition Committee, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Annual Report of the Dept. of Neurobiology and Behavior, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report of the Dept. of Crop and Soil Sciences, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Series II. Meetings and Conferences
  - Budget Conference: 127 Animal Science (FY 01-02Research, Extension Federal Formula Funds), 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Budget Conference: 121 Applied Economics and Management (FY 01-02 Research, Federal Formula Funds (FFF)), February 27, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Budget Conference: 124 Earth and Atmosperic Science (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), February 23, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Budget Conference: 137 Education (FY01-02 (Research, FFF), February 21, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Budget Conference: 139 Entomogy (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), March 1, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Budget Conference: 143 Food Science (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), February 21, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Budget Conference: 145 Horticulture (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), February 23, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Budget Conference: 146 Landscape Architecture (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), February 20, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Budget Conference: 165 Molecular Biology and Genetics (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), March 2, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Budget Conference: 147 Natural Resources (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), February 28, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Budget Conference: 159 Rural Sociology (FY 01-02 Research, FFF) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Budget Conference: 185 Plant Biology (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), March 7, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Budget Conference: 149 Plant Breeding (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), March 1, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Budget Conference: 153 Plant Pathology (FY 01-02 Research, FFF), February 27, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 2001 LIHREL Planning and Budget Conference, March 28, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chairs and Directors Meetings, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Chairs and Directors Meetings, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Chairs and Directors Meetings, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chairs and Directors Meetings, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chairs and Directors Meetings, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Chairs and Directors Meetings, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Chairs and Directors Meetings, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Department Chairs Meetings (1), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Department Chairs Meetings (2), 2001 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Department Chairs Meetings, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Department Chairs Meetings (1), 2003 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Department Chairs Meetings (2), 2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Department Chairs Meetings, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Department Chairs Meetings, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Department Chairs Meetings, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Department Chairs Meetings, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Department Chairs Meetings, Dec. 2007-April 2008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Department Chairs Meetings, May 2008-Dec. 2008 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Aug.-Dec. 2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Jan.-Feb. 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, March-April 2001 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, May-July 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, August-Sept. 2001 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Oct.-Dec. 2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, January 2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, February 2002 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, March-April 2002 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, May-August 2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Sept.-Oct. 2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Nov.-Dec. 2002 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Jan.-Feb. 2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, March-May 2003 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, June 2003 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, July-Sept. 2003 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Oct.-Dec. 2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Jan.-March 2004 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, April-June 2004 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, July-Sept. 2004 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Oct.-Dec. 2004 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Jan.-March 2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, April-August 2005 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Sept.-Dec. 2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Jan.-March 2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, April-June 2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, July-August 2006 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Sept.-Oct. 2006 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Nov.-Dec. 2006 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Jan.-Feb. 2007 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, March-April 2007 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, May-August 2007 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Sept.-Oct. 2007 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Nov.-Dec. 2007 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Jan.-Feb. 2008 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, March 2008 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, April-June 2008 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, July-Sept. 2008 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Associate Deans Meetings, Oct.-Dec. 2008 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Dean's Executive Council Meeting Minutes (1), Jan. 1999- June 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Dean's Executive Council Meeting Minutes (2), Jan. 1999- June 2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Dean's Executive Council Meeting Minutes (3), Jan. 1999- June 2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dean's Council, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dean's Council 2003 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Series III. Outreach, Programs, and Initiatives
  - Cornell Laboritory of Ornithology (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Environment Outreach Executive Summary (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Environmental Outreach Schools and Departments (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Environmental Outreach (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Environmental Outreach Center of the Environment (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Academic Program Budget and Planning Conference, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Accreditation Self Study for the International Association for Management Education, October 1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - AACSB - Business Accreditation Committee, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - NE Sun Grant Initiative (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Core Programs: Agriculture and Food Markets and Policy - Atmospheric Science (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Core Programs: Basic Biochemical Mechanisms - Business Management (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Core Programs: Cell Biology - Controlled Environmental Agriculture (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Core Programs: Dairy Systems (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Core Programs: Ecosystem Biology Program - Evolutionary Biology Program (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Core Programs: Farming Alternatives - Fungal Biology (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Core Programs: Human Communication Systems and Processes - Human Nutrition (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Core Programs: Information Systems and Technologies - International Nutrition Program (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Core Programs: Landscape Architecture - Landscape Management (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Core Programs: Marine Services - Molecular/Cellular Plant - Microbe Interactions (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Core Programs: Neurobiology - Nutritional Biochemistry (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Core Programs: Ornamentals and Urban IPM (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Core Programs: Plant Breeding and Genetics - Prokaryotic Biology (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Core Programs: Resource Policy, Managemnt and Human Dimensions - Risk Communication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Core Programs: Science and Citizenship Education - Systematic Biology (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Core Programs: Teacher Education - Tropical Farming Systems (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Core Programs: Vegetable Crops Systems - Vertebrate Biology (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Core Programs: Waste Management - Wetlands (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Don't Be Embarrassed! Talk about colorectal cancer with your health care provider! (Box 1)
    Videocassette, DVD, and brochures. In English and Spanish.
  - Core Programs: Agriculture Council (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Core Programs: Community, Human and Rural Development Council (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Core Programs: Environmental and Natural Resources Council (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Core Programs: Food and Nutrition Council (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Core Programs: International Council (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Core Programs: Life Sciences Council (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Series IV. Retreats
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Annual Reports (1), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Annual Reports (2), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Annual Reports (3), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (1), July 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (2), July 2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (3), July 2002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (1), June 2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Associate Deans Retreat(2), June 2003 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (3), June 2003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (1), 2004 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (2), 2004 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (3), 2004 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (1), 2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (2), 2005 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (3), 2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Budget and Data Analysis - Ithaca and Geneva (1), 2005 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Budget and Data Analysis - Ithaca and Geneva (2), 2005 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (1), 2006 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (2), 2006 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (3), 2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (1), 2007 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (2), 2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (3), 2007 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Associate Deans Retreat (4), 2007 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Binder 1 - #1, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Binder 1 - #2, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Binder 1 - #3, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Binder 1 - #4, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Binder 1 - #5, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Binder 2 - #1, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Binder 2 - #2, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Binder 2 - #3, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Associate Deans Retreat - Binder 2 - #4, June 2008 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Series V. Videos
  - Cornell Centennial - May 12 Parade, V-5333 (Box 9)
  - Cornell University - "125 Years of Creating the Future" - James Maas Prod., 1990; V-5334 (Box 9)
  - Reaching the Top - Three Success Stories - The 1991 Personal Enterprise Forum, April 1, 1991; V-5335 (Box 9)
  - Indigenous Preservation Networking Center - "Preserving the Natural Ways", June 1992; V-5336 (Box 9)
  - Statutory Colleges at Cornell: Service to the State, Nation and the World, October 13, 1992; V-5337 (Box 9)
  - Suburban Deer Management - Voices/Views/Visions, September 1993; V-5338 (Box 9)
  - Inside Albany - Gov's Conference on AgSci and Technology, November 9-10, 1993; V-5339 (Box 9)
  - War Memorial, V-5340 (Box 9)
  - Endowment for the Planet, V-5341 (Box 9)
  - Academic Leadership Workshop Series, April 15, 1994; V-5342 (Box 9)
  - Second Series: Academic Leadership Workshop, May 10, 1994; V-5343 (Box 9)
  - Cornell University's American Indian Program, V-5344 (Box 9)
  - The Skaneateles Lake Watershed Program - Dept. of Soil, Crop and Atmospheric Sciences, Cornell University and Cornell Cooperative Extension, V-5345 (Box 9)
  - Waterborne Pathogens: Research and Resource Management - Dept. of Soil, Crop and Atmospheric Sciences, Cornell University and Cornell Cooperative Extension, V-5346 (Box 9)
  - SUNY Video, V-5347 (Box 9)
  - Preparing for the Next Century: A Look at Cornell's College of Agriculture and Life Sciences - S-VHS Master, June 1995; V-5348 (Box 9)
  - Preparing for the Next Century: A Look at Cornell's College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, June 1995; V-5349 (Box 9)
  - Preparing for the Next Century: A Look at Cornell's College of Agriculture and Life Sciences - S-VHS Master, October 1995; V-5350 (Box 9)
  - Preparing for the Next Century: A Look at Cornell's College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, October 1995; V-5351 (Box 9)
  - Food Science: A Proud Past and a Promising Future, V-5352 (Box 9)
  - Maple Production School - Part 1, January 20, 1996; V-5353 (Box 9)
  - Maple Production School - Part 2, January 20, 1996; V-5354 (Box 9)
  - Rethinking SUNY Report: Panel, January 31, 1996; V-5355 (Box 9)
  - Symposium on Plant Biotechnology Issues: Risk Assessment, November 6, 1996; V-5356 (Box 9)
  - 3 Minutes from Our 35th Reunion, V-5357 (Box 9)
  - 21st Century Land Grant University - Reworking Success: New Communities, September 4, 1997; V-5358 (Box 9)
  - SUNY Chancellor John W. Ryan, April 25, 1997; V-5359 (Box 9)
  - Dateline NBC - Cornell Student Product Development Team Competition, August 15, 1997; V-5360 (Box 9)
  - Changing Expectations of Faculty Roles and Responsibilities, V-5361 (Box 9)
  - CALS/CCE Plant and Animal Initiative Update, November 6, 1998; V-5362 (Box 9)
  - 21st Century Land Grant Universities: Action on Issues - Kellog Commission on the Future of State and Land Grant Universities Panel Discussion, February 26, 1998; V-5363 (Box 9)
  - Cornell Associates - Harry Lawless, January 14, 1999; V-5364 (Box 9)
  - Cornell Associates - Terry Acree, January 14, 1999; V-5365 (Box 9)
  - Cornell Associates - James Bell, January 14, 1999; V-5366 (Box 9)
  - Cornell Associates - Elizabeth Earle, January 14, 1999; V-5367 (Box 9)
  - Cornell Associates - John Brady, January 14, 1999; V-5368 (Box 9)
  - Cornell Associates - Michael Shuler, January 14, 1999; V-5369 (Box 9)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension - 4-H External Review: Countdown to Action, February 26, 1999; V-5370 (Box 9)
  - CCE Director Candidate Presentations - Andy Novakovic, V-5371 (Box 9)
  - CCE Director Candidate Presentations - Andy Novakovic, V-5372 (Box 9)
  - CCE Director Candidate Presentations - Merrill Ewert, V-5373 (Box 9)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Video Report, V-5374 (Box 9)
  - Policy Development Videoconference, July 19, 2000; V-5375 (Box 9)
  - Dean Susan Henry - Presentation to Trustee Council, October 2000; V-5376 (Box 9)
  - Revitalizing Cornell Cooperative Extension - D. Merrill Ewert, September 16, 2000; V-5377 (Box 10)
  - Statewide Connection, October 11, 2001; V-5378 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - Rui Hai Liu, January 19, 2001; V-5379 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - Kathyrn Boor, January 19, 2001; V-5380 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - Karl Siebert, January 19, 2001; V-5381 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - Stephen Kresovich, January 19, 2001; V-5382 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - Randall Peterson, January 19, 2001; V-5383 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - T. Henick-Kling, January 19, 2001; V-5384 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - John S. Roberts, May 31, 2001; V-5385 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - Susan Henry, May 31, 2001; V-5386 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - X. G. Lei, May 31, 2001; V-5387 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - Martin Wiedmann, May 31, 2001; V-5388 (Box 10)
  - Cornell Associates - Kathryn Boor, May 31, 2001; V-5389 (Box 10)
  - Susan Henry's Address, April 30, 2003; V-5390 (Box 10)
  - Fruits, Vegetables, and Food Safety: Health and Hygiene on the Farm (Spanish; DVD), 2004; DVD-594 (Box 10)
  - Addressing Public Issues through Education, 1995; V-5425 (Box 10)
  - Second Tuesday Videos
    - CCESN 2nd Tuesday (Parent Resource Center, Broome County), V-5391 (Box 10)
    - CCESN 2nd Tuesday, September 1994; V-5406 (Box 10)
    - Second Tuesday, January 1, 1999; V-5407 (Box 10)
    - Second Tuesday - The State of Extension, May 11, 1999; V-5408 (Box 10)
    - Second Tuesday, November 9, 1999; V-5409 (Box 10)
    - Second Tuesday, May 9, 2000; V-5410 (Box 10)
    - Second Tuesday, September 12, 2000; V-5411 (Box 10)
    - Second Tuesday, November 14, 2000; V-5412 (Box 10)
    - Second Tuesday, March 13, 2001; V-5413 (Box 10)
    - Second Tuesday, May 8, 2001; V-5414 (Box 10)
- Series VI. Speeches
  - Speech Support Summary, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Speech Support Summary (1), 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Speech Support Summary (2), 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Speech Support Summary, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Series VII. Gifts to the Dean
  - Official Gifts Received from Representatives of Various Global Universities (Box 2)
- Series VIII. Subject Files
  - Mann - History, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Mann - Janet McCue, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Mann - Million Book Project, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Mann - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Mann - Note Cards, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Mann -Renovation, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Mann - TEEAL, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Mann - Reorganization, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Lab of Ornithology, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Lab of Ornithology - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Plantations - Annual Report, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Plantations - Audit Report, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Plantations - College Ponds, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Plantations - Advisory Board, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Polson - Global Development, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Polson - Rural Sociology, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Shoals Marine Lab, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Shoals Marine Lab, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Shoals Marine Lab, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Shoals - Jim Morin, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Animal Science - Annual Report, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Animal Science - Advisory Council, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Animal Science - Budget, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Animal Science - Correspondence, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Animal Science - Department Review, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Animal Science - Development/Fundraising, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Animal Science - Large Animal, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Animal Science - Name Change, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Animal Science -Pro-Dairy, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Animal Science - Pro-Dairy, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Animal Science - Sheep Program, July 2001 - July 2011 (Box 12, Folder 31)